imikimi.com 2018-08-24

# Imikimi Zo Privacy Policies - Imikimi Zo Privacy Policies

## Our Commitment to Your Privacy

We are committed to helping you, our Imikimi Zo customer to

  * share your positive contributions 
  * express yourself creatively 
  * discover and deepen your connection with others 
  * easily and fully control your privacy 

We charge you a small fee to make it possible to do those things. We do not sell or share your data with 3rd parties. That makes your privacy and your control over your digital social life SO much easier!

  * You pay us to work for you, our customer. 
  * Other, ad-supported sites get paid by 3rd parties you don’t even know, to package up all of the data of your digital life, for purposes you have little control over. You are not their customer, you are their product. 

Note: We do work with 3rd party services, but we do so solely for the purpose of serving you. These services include, but are not limited to: data storage, servers, analytics, and contacting you.

## You Control Your Privacy

We invented “Streams” so you could control your sharing and privacy for each group of people you interact with. Your profile picture, your display-name and whether or not you are a 'member' are publicly viewable. The rest of your privacy is control Stream-byStream. Currently, there are two kinds of Streams:

  * Private Streams: By default, private streams are only viewable by you. You can share your private streams with others by sharing one or more posts from that Stream. Whomever you share a post with will be able to see and comment on any post in that same Stream. This allows you to choose, on a Stream-by-Stream basis, who sees your content. 
  * Public Streams: Anybody can see your public Streams. 

## Deleting and Changing Your Content

You can change your e-mail and your account name on your Profile page. You can delete Posts individually any time your are logged in, under the 3-dot menu when you are on the Post. 

We are working on tools to help you delete Streams and your whole Account more easily. In the mean time, if you wish to delete your account, please contact us directly. You can delete individual Posts, and if it is the last post in a Stream, the Stream will be automatically deleted. 

## Imikimi Privacy Policy Details

Imikimi LLC. ("Imikimi") recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others who use www.Imikimi.com or other web sites owned or operated by Imikimi (the "Imikimi Sites") (collectively or individually "Users") value their privacy. This Privacy Notice details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the Imikimi Sites. Imikimi provides this Privacy Notice to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the Imikimi Sites. 

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the Imikimi Terms of Use. Your use of the Imikimi Sites and any personal information you provide on the Imikimi Sites remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use. 

Please note that image, video, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the Imikimi Sites becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Notice. 

## The Information Imikimi Collects

User Provided Information: You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to Imikimi when choosing to participate in various activities on the Imikimi Sites such as uploading images and photographs, customizing images, e-mailing images, posting messages, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. 

Cookies Information: When you visit the Imikimi Sites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Imikimi uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Imikimi Sites may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

Log File Information: When you use the Imikimi Sites, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

Clear GIFs Information: When you use the Imikimi Sites, we may employ "clear GIFs" (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users anonymously (i.e., in a non-personally-identifiable manner). In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. 

## The Way Imikimi Uses Information

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the Imikimi Sites, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Imikimi Sites. 

Any personal information or image content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload and modify images or send messages through the Imikimi Sites and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any images that you submit to the Imikimi Sites may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Imikimi Site changes or for customer service purposes). 

We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Imikimi Sites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends. 

We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Imikimi Sites; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. 

## When Imikimi Discloses Information

We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Imikimi Sites. 

We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. 

Imikimi also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that Imikimi believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Imikimi, our Users or others. 

## Your Choices About Privacy

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Imikimi Sites, in which case Imikimi may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page. Please note that image and media files uploaded by Users to the Imikimi Sites cannot be removed and remain subject to our Terms of Use. 

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. 

Please contact Imikimi with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, your consent, or your opt-in or opt-out choices using this contact form. 

## Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

Imikimi allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Imikimi Sites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Imikimi Sites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. 

Imikimi does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Imikimi to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, women ages 25-34) or audience segment (for example, women ages 25-44 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Imikimi Sites, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks (see links below) for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Imikimi's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

For more information, please visit [http://networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/). 

Currently, Imikimi has relationships with the following third-party ad servers or ad networks: 

  * Google, Inc. [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html)

## Our Commitment To Data Security

Imikimi uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Imikimi and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Imikimi makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If Imikimi learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Imikimi may post a notice on the Imikimi Sites if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us using this contact form. 

## Our Commitment To Childrens' Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Imikimi does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the Imikimi Sites from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Imikimi Sites at any time or in any manner. If Imikimi learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the Imikimi Sites without verified parental consent, then Imikimi will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

## Special Note to International Users

The Imikimi Sites are hosted in the United States and are intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing the Imikimi Sites from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Imikimi Sites, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. 

## In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy

In the event that Imikimi is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used. 

## Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "effective date" below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of the Imikimi Sites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions. 

For revisions to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personal information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information. 

## Date Last Modified:

This Privacy Notice was last modified May 22, 2007.

## Contact Information:

Please contact Imikimi with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice using this contact form.
